

MATTHEW CURRAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | WWW.MATTHEWCURRAN.TECH

OBJECTIVE

I am an experienced professional focused on continuous improvement. I have a proven history of technical mastery in all previous positions. I am skilled in handling multiple projects and exceeding quality standards. I seek an entry level position as a junior developer.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, Ajax, Express, Node, MySQL, Mongo, Handlebars, React, GIT, GitHub

EXPERIENCE

AUTO ADJUSTER • ALLSTATE • 2015 - ONGOING

- Negotiate, assess and compile auto repair estimates.
- Trained employees on standard operating procedures and new technologies.
- · Periodically lead team meetings.
- Continually exceeded quality and production goals.

ASSISTANT MANAGER • B&B AUTO BODY • 2009 - 2014

- Tracked vehicles ensuring low repair cycle time.
- Performed quality control during and after repairs.
- Assembled and disassembled vehicles.
- Used scan tools to diagnose trouble codes.

INFANTRY FIRE TEAM LEADER • US ARMY • 2004 – 2009

- Alpha team leader responsible for a four-man fire team.
- Lead combat patrols during Operation Iraqi Freedom.
- Subject matter expert on all assigned weapon systems.
- Expert Infantry Badge recipient.

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOT CAMP • 2018 • UNC CHARLOTTE

• An intensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to designing and building web applications using a MERN stack.

B.S. PSYCHOLOGY • 2012 • SAINT THOMAS AOUINAS

- Psi Chi Honor Society
- 3.78 GPA

A.A LIBERAL ARTS • 2010 • ROCKLAND COMMUNITY COLLEGE

- Phi Theta Kapa Honor Society
- 3.9 GPA







